Finding Aid for Paris Grange No. 19 (Kent County, Mich.) records, 1873-1894 and 1900-1966
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
Paris Grange No. 19 (Kent County, Mich.) records 1873-1894 and 1900-1966
Paris Grange No. 19 (Kent County, Mich.)
1 linear foot
851986 Bg 2
Kent County, Michigan grange chapter; minutes and account books.
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
The record group was donated by Cyrus Jasperse (donor no. 4229 ).
The record group is open to research.
Paris Grange No. 19, Kent County, Michigan was established April 10, 1873. Paris Grange ceased formal activities from approximately 1917 to 1921. It was then formally reorganized in 1922. Paris Grange closed its activities in 1983.
The record group consists of minute books, 1873-1966, with some gaps (1895-1904 and 1917-1921). There are also two account books, 1900-1915 and 1943-1952.
Subjects:
Agriculture--Michigan--Kent County.; Grand Rapids (Mich.); Kent County (Mich.); Paris (Kent County, Mich.: Township); Paris Grange, No. 19 (Kent County, Mich.)
- Minute Books
  - Minutes, 1873-1876 (Box 1)
  - Minutes, 1877-1882 (Box 1)
  - Minutes, 1884-1894 (Box 1)
  - Minutes, 1905-1916 (Box 1)
  - Minutes, 1922-1926 (Box 1)
  - Minutes, 1926-1929 (Box 1)
  - Minutes, 1929-1931 (Box 1)
  - Minutes, 1931-1933 (Box 1)
  - Minutes, 1933-1935 (Box 1)
  - Minutes, 1935-1936 (Box 1)
  - Minutes, 1936-1937 (Box 1)
  - Minutes, 1937-1939 (Box 1)
  - Minutes, 1939-1941 (Box 1)
  - Minutes, 1941-1944 (Box 1)
  - Minutes, 1944-1946 (Box 1)
  - Minutes, 1946-1949 (Box 1)
  - Minutes, 1949-1956 (Box 1)
  - Minutes, 1956-1966 (Box 1)
- Account Books
  - Account book, 1900-1915 (Box 1)
  - Account book, 1943-1952 (Box 1)